<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>indices on bjornar.dev</title>
    <link>https://bjornar.dev/nb-no/index/</link>
    <description>Recent content in indices on bjornar.dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://bjornar.dev/nb-no/index/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bjornar.dev/nb-no/index/section-2-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bjornar.dev/nb-no/index/section-2-2/</guid>
      <description>Work experience Adstate Full-stack developer
2020 ⟶ present
Datahjelpen CEO, developer &amp;amp; designer
2016 ⟶ present
Optimale Systemer Developer
2014 ⟶ 2016
Devloper experience HTML CSS, SASS JS, ES6, NodeJS React, Vue, Angular PHP, Wordpress, Laravel MySQL Git Docker, k8s, Helm Other experience Figma Photoshop </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career</title>
      <link>https://bjornar.dev/nb-no/index/section-2-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bjornar.dev/nb-no/index/section-2-1/</guid>
      <description>I learnt HTML, CSS, JS and PHP through self study and got a few gigs through some close friends. Later on I got my first real job as an apprentice at Optimale Systemer in Larvik. Around the same time I met my now wife, we started the company Datahjelpen together so we could take on extra jobs outside of work and school.
After 2 years at Optimale Systemer I had learned a lot and considered myself a full-stack web developer, though still very much a junior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personlig</title>
      <link>https://bjornar.dev/nb-no/index/section-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bjornar.dev/nb-no/index/section-1/</guid>
      <description>Født og oppvokst i Larvik, Norge. Bor i Sandefjord med min fantastiske kone og vår søte hund.
I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved building and taking things apart, so when I at a young age was introduced to computers, it didn&amp;rsquo;t take very long before I was taking them apart and learning about how they worked. When I was 14 I saved up scholarship money originally ment for school equipment to instead buy computer parts so I could build my first desktop computer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
